Guide to the Frank Baker papers, 1641-2002 and undated, bulk 1740-1995 RL.00069
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Baker Collections Files Series, 1955-2001 and undated, 3 boxes
  - Correspondence and additions, 1960-2001, Folders 1-4 of 9 (Box 1)
    Arranged in reverse chronological order. Folder 9 contains Baker's original list of materials sold to the library circa 1960.
  - Correspondence and Additions, 1960-2001, Folders 5-9 of 9 (Box 2)
  - Eighteenth century publications project, 1983 and undated, Folder 1-6 of 11 (Box 2)
    Photocopies of title pages of 18th century publications received by the library from Frank Baker, as of 1983. Photocopies were made for Dr. Baker's personal files and then returned at a later date. Arranged as received, alphabetically by title.
  - Eighteenth Century Publications Project, 1983 and undated, Folder 7-11 of 11 (Box 3)
  - Negotiations with Kingston-upon-Hull to house on loan, 1955-1964 (Box 3)
  - Purchases and sales, 1965-1966, 1983-1990, and undated, 6 folders (Box 3)
    Lists of potential purchases and sales of Methodistica and Wesleyana, from and to various private dealers and libraries other than Duke University.
- Correspondence Series, 1931-2000 and undated, 9 boxes
  Arranged chronologically to folder level but not necessarily chronological within folders.
  - Alphabetical Correspondence Subseries, 1938-1997 and undated
    Letters to and from frequent correspondents among Baker's professional colleagues and personal acquaintances. The most substantive correspondence here--in extent and content--is with publisher Frank Cumbers and Methodist scholars Oliver Beckerlegge, John Lawson, and John Vickers. Arranged alphabetically by name, organization, or topic.
    - Albin, Tom (Thomas R.), 1979-1981 (Box 4)
    - Baker, Albert E. and Hannah, 1973-1994 (Box 4)
    - Baker, Nellie, 1953-1994 (Box 4)
    - Beckerlegge, Oliver, 1944-1997 and undated (Box 4)
    - Bowmer, John, 1945-1995 (Box 4)
    - Bridwell Library (Southern Methodist University, Perkins School of Theology), 1962-1994 (Box 4)
    - Chambers, Wesley A. and Maida, 1977-1995 (Box 4)
    - Chilcote, Paul, 1990-1995 (Box 4)
    - Cumbers, Frank, 1947-1990 (Box 4)
    - Davies, Rupert, 1981-1984 (Box 4)
    - Dews, Colin, 1978-1995 (Box 4)
    - Drew University Library, 1975-1993 (Box 4)
    - Duke University Libraries, 1977-1995 (Box 4)
      Correspondence with the staff of Duke University Libraries also appears in other series, most extensively under correspondence in the Baker Collections Files.
    - Epworth Press / Epworth Secondhand Books, 1938-1987 (Box 4)
    - Farris, Donn Michael, 1960-1991 (Box 4)
    - Foxon, David, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
    - Fraser, Robert, 1987-1988 (Box 4)
    - Green, Charles A., 1989-1995 (Box 4)
    - Hart, Elizabeth, 1989-1993 (Box 4)
    - Heitzenrater, Richard, 1969-1993 and undated (Box 4)
    - Hildebrandt, Franz, 1954-1960, 1985-1986 (Box 5)
    - Hymns: Correspondence on John Wesley and the German Hymn and John Wesley's First Hymn Book, 1958, 1970-1981 (Box 5)
    - Inter Documentation Company, 1979-1988, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - John Rylands University Library, University of Manchester, 1980-1995 (Box 5)
    - Kimbrough, S. T. (Steve), 1986-1997 (Box 5)
    - Kline, Larry (Lawrence O.), 1964, 1976, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
    - Lawson, John, 1944, 1958-1995 (Box 5)
    - Leary, William, 1975-1991 and undated (Box 5)
    - Lenton, John, 1984-1995 (Box 5)
    - Lynch, Elizabeth, 1995 (Box 5)
    - Maddox, Randy L., 1988-1991 (Box 5)
    - Maser, Frederick E., 1972-1995 (Box 5)
    - Matthews, Rex. D., 1990-1994 (Box 5)
    - McGonigle, Herbert, 1980-1995 (Box 5)
    - Methodist Church--various divisions, 1957-1984 (Box 5)
    - Outler, Albert C., 1994 (Box 5)
    - Shipman, Kathleen, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
    - Swift, Wesley F., 1945-1961 (Box 5)
    - Vickers, John, 1953-1994 and undated (Box 5)
    - Wood, W.R., 1989-1991 (Box 5)
    - Zimmerman, George, 1990-1991 (Box 5)
  - Chronological Correspondence Subseries, 1931-2000 and undated
    Correspondence prior to 1960, when Baker still lived in England, may be particularly of note to researchers interested in the provenance of materials in the various Baker collections at Duke. These letters often refer to his attempts to discover and acquire Wesleyan and Methodist research materials in the possession of private individuals, professional dealers, churches, local historical societies, and other organizations. The content of folders covering this period may range from itemized receipts to lengthy discussions and evaluations of the subject matter and authenticity of materials. Arranged chronologically to the year level.
    - 1931-1939 (Box 6)
    - 1940-1949, 9 folders (Box 6)
    - 1950-1952, 3 folders (Box 6)
    - 1953-1958, 9 folders (Box 7)
    - 1959, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - 1960-1964, 6 folders (Box 8)
    - 1965-1969, 5 folders (Box 9)
    - 1970-1975, 6 folders (Box 9)
    - 1976-1979, 4 folders (Box 10)
    - 1980-1983, 5 folders (Box 10)
    - 1984-1989, 8 folders (Box 11)
    - 1990, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - 1991-2000, 13 folders (Box 12)
    - Undated items (Box 12)
- Libraries and Archives Series, circa 1930-circa 1990 and undated, 4 boxes
  Materials compiled during Frank Baker's correspondence with and/or visits to libraries, archives, and historical societies all over the English-speaking world, related to a variety of projects over several decades. Arranged in two subseries, American Collections and International Collections.
  - American Collections Subseries, circa 1960-circa 1990 and undated, 49 folders
    Arranged as received, alphabetically by state.
    - List of Library Codes (Box 13)
    - Alabama-New Hampshire, circa 1960-circa 1990 and undated, 23 folders (Box 13)
      Significant holdings: Wesleyan University, Library of Congress, Wesley Theological Seminary, Emory, Asbury, Baltimore, New England Methodist History Society, Boston Public Library, Harvard University, American Antiquarian Society
    - New Jersey-Texas, circa 1960-circa 1990 and undated, 21 folders (Box 14)
      Significant holdings: Drew, New York Public Library, General Theological Seminary, Pierpont Morgan Library, Union Theological Seminary, Duke, Lake Junaluska, Philadelphia, St. George's Collection
    - Texas-Wisconsin, circa 1960-circa 1990 and undated, 5 folders (Box 15)
      Significant holdings: Methodist Publishing House, Southern Methodist University
  - International Collections Subseries, circa 1930-1987 and undated, 46 folders
    Arranged as received, alphabetically by geographical area. Collections in England are arranged to the level of county (or city, in some cases); collections elsewhere are arranged to the level of country.
    - Australia and New Zealand, 1980, 1982, 1987 and undated, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Canada, 1973-1987 and undated, 1 folders (Box 15)
      Significant holdings: Newfoundland
    - England, circa 1930-circa 1980 and undated, 13 folders (Box 15)
      Significant holdings: Bristol, Methodist Archives (London)
    - England, circa 1930-circa 1980 and undated, 21 folders (Box 16)
      Significant holdings: Methodist Archives (Univ. of Manchester), Oxford, Richmond
    - Ireland, 1964-1974 and undated, 2 folders (Box 16)
      Significant holdings: Belfast (Wesley Historical Society)
    - Italy, 1973 and undated, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Scotland, 1974 and undated, 1 folders (Box 16)
    - South Africa, 1970-1977 and undated, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Wales, 1969-1974 and undated, 1 folders (Box 16)
- Ministry Series, 1926-1987 and undated, 7 boxes
  Administrative files, church roll books, files from specific churches and circuits, notes and outlines for many sermons, and a clippings file arranged by topic, possibly as a source of anecdotes and examples to use in sermons. Series is arranged alphabetically by category, with the exception that clippings are housed at the end.
  - Administrative files: Candidates for the Ministry, 1954-1957, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Administrative files: Church roll books, 1947-1955 (Box 17)
  - Administrative files: Members, undated (Box 17)
  - Administrative files: Hull, 21 Ash Grove, undated (Box 17)
  - Administrative files: Ministerial Training Committee, 1957-1959 (Box 17)
  - Administrative files: Miscellaneous, 1957-1959 and undated (Box 17)
  - Administrative files: Retirement, 1956-1987 (Box 17)
  - Circuit youth, undated (Box 17)
  - Colorado Conference scrapbook, 1953 (Box OV 1)
  - Methodist Central Buying Association, 1959 and undated (Box 17)
  - Methodist Circuit, Hull, 1956-1959 (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous, 1952-1959 and undated (Box 17)
  - Notes, various topics, undated (Box 18)
  - Play: "The Little Lord Jesus" by Frank Baker, undated (Box 18)
  - Photographic material, undated (Box 18)
  - Printed material, 1945-1959 and undated (Box 18)
  - Religious teaching, undated (Box 18)
  - Sermons, undated, Folders 1-5 of 12 (Box 18)
  - unspecified, Folders 6-12 of 12 (Box 19)
  - Sermons illustrations and anecdotes, undated (Box 19)
  - Sermon notebooks, 1926-1960 and undated, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Tools for the Job, 1953-1956 and undated, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Trinity Church focus meetings, undated (Box 20)
  - Trust documents, 1953 and undated (Box 20)
  - Working Lads' Institute and Home, undated (Box 20)
  - Youth committees, undated (Box 20)
  - Clippings, 1938-1954 and undated, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Clippings files, circa 1935-circa 1950 (Box 21-22)
    Two boxes of clippings on various topics, arranged alphabetically; apparently to be used as a resource for illustrating sermons, homilies, articles, etc.
- Personal Files Series, circa 1920-1994 and undated, 6 boxes plus oversize items
  Personal papers of Frank Baker (FB), including artwork, ephemera and memorabilia, financial papers and travel-related material. Arranged alphabetically by category. The 1920s Primitive Methodist materials housed under "Awards, certificates, and diplomas" constitute fairly late documents in the history of the church, prior to unification of the Methodist Church in 1932.
  - Accession book: list of 1,360 books, apparently owned by FB, undated (Box 23)
  - Artifact: magnifying loupe, undated (Box 238)
  - Artwork by FB, circa 1920 and undated, 3 folders (Box 23, OV 1, and OV 7)
  - Artwork by others, 1986 and undated, 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Awards, certificates, and diplomas, 1920-1983, 8 folders (Box 23 and OV 1)
    Honors awarded to Baker throughout his life, ranging from a Primitive Methodist Sunday School Scripture Examination Second Prize in the early 1920s to an honorary Doctor of Divinity degree presented by Asbury Theological Seminary in 1983. Also included here are various church and Sunday school certificates awarded to his wife and children, mainly from the 1950s. Oversize materials (folders 6-8) include secondary school and undergraduate awards and diplomas for Frank Baker; Primitive Methodist Teacher Training School certificates for Ellen Levitt and Frank Baker, 1920s; honorary citizen of Tennessee award for Frank Baker.
  - Biographical--miscellaneous clippings and printed material, 1973-1990 (Box 23)
  - Booksellers - list of booksellers 1941-onwards in British Isles; list of purchases, prices, 1941 and undated (with F. Baker's name on inside cover) (Box 23)
  - Boy Scouts of America--Asbury Trail Award pamphlet, 1953 (Box 23)
  - Calendars and contacts, 1930s-1980s and undated (Box 24)
    Approximately fifty datebooks, pocket calendars and diaries, and lists of contacts. Although longer notes appear on a few inserted pages, most entries are brief.
  - Career--published bibliographies and biographies, 1956-1991, 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Career--Frank Baker literary property and royalties, 1938-1972 (Box 25)
  - Christmas cards and newsletters--family cards and cards organized by theme and imagery, 1934-1958 and undated, 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Durham Civic Choral Society--newsletters, programs, and rosters, 1962-1969, 3 folders (Box 25)
  - Financial and legal papers, 1916-1994 and undated, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 25)
  - Financial and legal papers, 1916-1994 and undated, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 26)
  - Memorabilia and miscellaneous cards and printed material, 1939-1992 and undated, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - Music--miscellaneous songs and sheet music, 1924 and undated (Box 26)
  - Philately--correspondence, clippings, printed materials, and newsletters of the Methodist Philatelic Society and the American Society of Polar Philatelists, 1971-1991 and undated, Folders 1-4 of 7 (Box 26)
  - Philately--correspondence, clippings, printed materials, and newsletters of the Methodist Philatelic Society and the American Society of Polar Philatelists, 1971-1991 and undated, Folders 5-7 of 7 (Box 27)
  - Photographs, 1948-1993 and undated (Box 27)
  - Individual portrait photographs of Frank Baker's parents, Frank and Annie Elizabeth Baker, circa 1908 (Box OVSZ 1)
  - Register of borrowed books and papers, 1944-1957 and undated (Box 27)
    Notebook used for multiple purposes, including reading notes on Middle English and register of books and papers borrowed by various members from Wesley Historical Society. Correspondence and miscellaneous inserts removed to separate folders; correspondents include Oliver Beckerlegge and Frank Cumbers.
  - Student years: FB's exam papers, 1928-1934 (Box 27)
  - Student years: Notebooks, 1935 and undated, 3 folders (Box 28)
  - Student years: Notes on various subjects, undated (Box 28)
  - Student years: Primitive Methodist Church exam papers, 1926-1930 (Box 28)
  - Student years: University of London--sample M.A. examinations, 1939-1944 (Box 28)
  - Student years: University of Nottingham--correspondence and printed material, 1948-1955 (Box 28)
  - Travel--miscellaneous, 1953-1956 (Box 28)
  - Travel--world tour, 1980 (Box 28)
  - Visitors book, 1947-1989 (Box 28)
- Printed Material Series, 1744-1999 and undated, 16 boxes, including oversize folders
  Arranged alphabetically by categories, with some categories repeated in oversize boxes listed at the end of the series.
  - Articles Subseries
    - Association of the British Theological and Philosophical Libraries, 1958-1980 (Box 29)
    - Book reviews, 1978-1988 and undated (Box 29)
    - Chapters from various books, 1967-1992 (Box 29)
    - Epworth Review, 1974-1987 (Box 29)
    - The Library, 1934-1994, 3 folders (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous, 1744-1849, Folders 1-4 of 17 (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous, 1850-1959, Folders 5-12 of 17 (Box 30)
    - Miscellaneous, 1960-1999 and undated, Folders 13-17 of 17 (Box 31)
  - Catalogues Subseries
    - Auction, 1957-1964, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Bibliographies, 1923-1988 and undated, folders 1-3 of 4 (Box 31)
    - Bibliographies, undated, circa 1930-1950, folder 4 of 4 (Box 32)
    - Exhibitions, 1929-1984, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - General book sales, 1938-1995 and undated, 5 folders (Box 32)
    - Microfilm, 1971-1981 and undated (Box 32)
    - Wesleyana sales, 1840-1975, folder 1 of 5 (Box 32)
    - Wesleyana sales, 1976-1991 and undated, Folders 2-5 of 5 (Box 33)
  - Maps Subseries, 120 items
    Miscellaneous 20th century maps. For 17th-19th century engraved maps, see Maps Subseries in the Frank Baker Collection of Wesleyana and British Methodism, Visual Materials Series.
    - Harmsworth Universal Atlas, circa 1900-1910, 35 items (Box OV 7)
    - Miscellaneous maps of English cities and counties, 1930-1952 and undated, 2 folders, 20 items (Box OV 3 and 7)
      Two ordnance maps of England and Wales for Scarborough and Ribblesdale, circa 1930. One copy of a hand-drawn map circa 1930, "The Yorkshire Martyrs. Priests and Laymen; Birthplaces and Date of Martyrdom." One hand-drawn map, undated, "The East Riding of Yorkshire. One print map of Lancashire, circa 1903. Two small print maps of Whitby, circa 1933. One print map, circa 1953, "Directory of Churches and Other Religious Organizations." One population density map, circa 1944, "The City and County of Kingston-Upon-Hull."
    - Ordnance maps--Lancashire and Yorkshire, 1911-1912, 36 sheets (Box OV 7)
    - Railroad maps--Britain, New Zealand, and the East India Tramways Co., 1949 and undated, 3 items (Box OV 7)
    - Miscellaneous modern maps, 1946-1969 and undated, 13 items (Box OV 8 [42x28 box])
      Various ordnance maps of Israel, Savannah, North Carolina, and other places; historical maps of North Carolina shipwrecks, early Colorado history, British Caribbean colonies, and other places.
    - Oversize maps--World War I era maps, 1916 and undated, 12 items (Box OV 8)
      Various ordnance maps and the series of Times Maps of the War.
    - Oversize maps of U.S., Labrador, Norway, and other places, 1952-1963 and undated, 13 items; 12 items (Oversize-folder 1)
      Various survey maps of United States, Labrador, Norway, and other places. Also includes color map of British abbeys and cathedrals, circa 1960s.
    - Map of British abbeys and cathedrals, undated (Oversize-folder 1)
    - Plans of Paris arrondisements, 1st-9th, circa 1920s, approx. 36x26 inches; 11 sheets (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Map of North American colonies, 1784, London publisher (modern reproduction) (Oversize-folder 3)
    - French map of siege of Savannah, Georgia, 1779 (modern reproduction) (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Ordnance maps of Lancashire, 1895-1903, 7 sheets (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Baker's hand-traced maps of Cleesthorpe in 1846, "Wesley's Moorfields and Spitalfields," and other places in England, circa 1930s, 6 sheets (Oversize-folder 5)
    - Southern Jurisdiction, Methodist Church, (United States) 1957 (Oversize-folder 5)
      Scope and Contents
      Color map of the Southern U.S., showing Methodist districts and their numbers (35 x 23 inches).
  - Methodist and Other Religious Materials Subseries
    - Bulletins, leaflets, and programs, 1900-1978, folders 1-6 of 9 (Box 33)
    - Bulletins, leaflets, and programs, 1980-1993 and undated, folders 7-9 of 9 (Box 34)
    - Magazines, newsletters, and pamphlets, 1907-1959, folders 1-6 of 14 (Box 34)
    - Magazines, newsletters, and pamphlets, 1960-1996 and undated, folders 7-14 of 14 (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous Materials Subseries
    - Israeli tourism, 1951-1958 (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous secular, 1924-1980 and undated (Box 36)
    - Temperance and social welfare, 1921-1948 and undated (Box 36)
  - Serials Subseries
    - Cirplan, 1955-1980 (Box 36)
    - The Hymn, October 1988 (Box 36)
    - The Hymn Society Bulletin, 1990-1993 (Box 36)
    - International Arbitration League, The Arbitrator, 1949-1950 (Box 36)
    - London Quarterly Review and Holborn Review, 1930-1959, folders 1-2 of 7 (Box 36)
    - London Quarterly Review and Holborn Review, 1930-1959, folders 3-7 of 7 (Box 37)
    - Wesleyan Methodist Magazine, 1901 (Box 37)
    - Wesleyan Historical Society, 1991-1995 (Box 37)
    - Single copies, 1939-1993, 4 folders (Box 38)
    - Serials, 1951, 1964, and undated (Box OV 3)
    - Serials- articles from Country Life, 1946-1949 (Box OV 3)
  - Clippings and Newspapers Subseries
    - Clippings, Baker events, 1945-1993 and undated (Box 38)
    - Clippings, 1880-1939, 6 folders (Box 38)
    - Clippings, 1940-1949, folders 1-2 of 3 (Box 38)
    - Clippings, 1940-1949, folder 3 of 3 (Box 39)
    - Clippings, 1950-1999 and undated, 7 folders (Box 39)
    - Clippings, 1858-1909 (Box OV 1)
    - Clippings, 1910-1949, 5 folders (Box OV 2)
      Contains 1939 Methodist Recorder issue celebrating 400th Anniversary of English Bible.
    - Clippings, 1950-1959, 6 folders (Box OV 2)
    - Clippings, 1960-1999 and undated, 3 folders (Box OV 3)
    - Newspapers, 1858, 1883, 1938-1991, and undated (Box OV 3)
    - Irish Christian Advocate, 1949, 1951, 1967, 15 issues (Box OV 3)
    - Joyful News, 1883, 1953-1958, 10 issues (Box OV 3)
    - Methodist Recorder, 1938-1982, 11 issues plus supplements (Box OV 3)
      Includes special issues for 400th anniversary of English Bible and 200th anniversary of JW's field preaching.
    - Various newspapers, single issues, 1858, 1949-1991, 3 folders (Box OV 3 and OV 7)
      Various newspapers, mainly from small towns in England. The 1858 item is The Congleton Advertiser (OV 7). Other exceptions to the general scope are a 1974 issue of Dimension: Newspaper of the Methodist Church of South Africa; and a 1961 issue of Vårtland, a Norwegian newspaper, reporting on Western protests over the raising of the Berlin Wall.
  - Visual Materials Subseries, 1921-1959 and undated, approximately 1000 items
    Arranged by categories, which include the following: calendars; oversize photographs; postcards of various historical figures and places in Great Britain and the United States; posters; prints of landscapes and religious images from various books, magazines, calendars, and other sources; and movie stills. Categories listed in box number order, as possible.
    - Movie stills, 1959 (Box 39)
    - Postcards, 1950s and undated, 4 folders, 600 items (Box 39)
    - Prints--landscapes and religious images, color and b/w, 1921-1959 and undated, 100 items (Box 39 and OV 3)
    - Calendars, 1979 (Box OV 4)
    - Shaw's model cut-out painting book, undated (Box OV 4)
    - Posters, undated, 2 folders, 18 items (Box OV 4 and 7)
    - Photographs, various European locales and architecture, undated, 5 items (Box OV 7)
    - Typeface specimen reproductions, 16th-18th centuries, circa 1960s (many sheets) (Oversize-folder 4)
  - Unsorted Print Materials, 8 folders
    - Various unsorted items collected by Baker, 1809-1964 and undated (Box 40)
    - Various oversize rolled items, various dates (Tube 1)
      Miscellaneous items collected by Frank Baker: posters, flyers, maps.
- Professional Service Series, 1930s-1990 and undated, 15 boxes
  - Engagements Subseries
    - Aldersgate Day, Acuff's Chapel, 1970 (Box 41)
    - American Methodist Bicentennial, 1966 (Box 41)
    - Association of Methodist Historical Societies, 1951-1956 (Box 41)
    - Australia, 1980 (Box 41)
    - Austria, 1958 (Box 41)
    - British Methodist Conference, 1950, 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Canadian Methodist Historical Society, 1980 (Box 41)
    - Colorado Conference, 1953, 3 folders (Box 41)
    - Conference on Christian Unity, 1958 (Box 41)
    - Drew University, 1974, 1983-1984, 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Ecumenical Methodist Conference, 1946-1951, 3 folders (Box 42)
    - Emory University, Bicentennial Consultation on Wesleyan Theology, 1983, 4 folders (Box 42)
    - England, 1976-1988, 4 folders (Box 42)
    - India, 1985, folder 1 of 2 (Box 42)
      Correspondence and various legal materials.
    - India, 1985, folder 2 of 2 (Box 43)
    - International Conference on Computers and the Humanities, 6th, 1983 (Box 43)
    - International Methodist Historical Society, 1948-1949, 1960, 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Japan, circa 1970-1980, 2 folders (Box 43)
      Correspondence, manuscripts, and printed material about a trip to Japan that took place circa 1978-1979. Some material, especially correspondence, appears to be unrelated unless this material documents more than one trip. Contains an abbreviated version of the article "John Wesley and the Bible" (Hart198, 1976), apparently to be delivered at a conference.
    - Lafayette Course of Greeting Card (Verse) Writing, 1937 (Box 43)
    - Methodist Goodwill Tour of Europe, 1951 (Box 43)
    - Methodist Education Committee, 1958 (Box 43)
    - Newland Parish Church and Newland Methodist Church Joint Conference, 1958 (Box 43)
    - New Zealand, undated (Box 43)
    - Oberammergau,1930 and undated, folders 1-5 of 7 (Box 43)